Thank you.
Pesci, what the hell
are you doing? Help me!
Stop this train right now, Pesci!
No way!
You have to stop this train!
Big bro but I don't know
the first thing about
stopping trains in a
matter of moments you and
Your power will be but a memory after that
I'll save my team and
I'll keep protecting Trish
Bucurati!
Damn you!
Big bro!
What?
I won't let this prick
take you away from me!
Nice!
That was marvelous work, Pass.
Your quick-fire thinking
prevented a nasty end.
Talk about a close one!
He was almost a goner, but I
snagged him at the last second,
and now that he's on my hook,
he's not going anywhere.
But it feels like I've got two bodies
dangling off the end of the line.
It must be Pucurati.
He didn't bite it when they fell.
You're a formidable adversary.
My life started to flash
before my eyes just then.
I know I said something to the
effect of you being a lousy Cape,
but I take it all back now.
That was said in poor taste.
I see now you make decisions
with a fair and impartial eye.
Your crew's lives are
as valuable as your own.
The more we duke it out,
the more apparent it is
the boss was right to
leave his estranged daughter
in your capable hands.
Yes, you've left quite
a strong impression.
However, Bucciarati, your
luck as a Cape just ran out!
You were so eager to leap
from this train before!
I hope you enjoy your ride
to the afterlife! Superman!
Superman!
Did you forget?
My aging powers are still thrusting
you into an early retirement!
Too slow!
It's funny.
Thanks to your younger brother's freaky
fishing line, my life has been spared.
What?
He wasn't aiming for me in the least.
Could I be the unlucky one in all of this?
Just look at what happened with Mista.
It's a miracle he still has a pulse.
I unloaded three bullets
straight into his skull,
yet somehow the stronzo
is still drawing breath.
None of this makes any sense.
It's as if the sun suddenly
started rising in the west!
I told him everything he needs to know.
The energy from an attack
dealt on the fishing
line goes straight back
to the one on the hook!
It can't be!
Curse you, Bucciarati!
Whoa, my load just got
a hell of a lot lighter.
Looks like I lost that douche, Bucciarati.
We did it, Prosciutto!
We slaughtered that punk!
His age acceleration
is finally wearing off.
Now we just have to
finish off, loser hook.
Yeah.
What the heck?
I know for a fact that I
hooked Big Bro's right hand.
And I'm positive there was
nothing else on the line.
His pinky.
I'm sure it was on the
right side of the hook.
But it's different now.
The pinky's on the left side of the hook.
But how is that possible?
How'd I hook the left hand?
What the heck is going on here?
Something weird's happening out there.
Why is my Big Bro's left hand hooked now?
Would someone make this
weird shit make sense?
Because I'm freaking the F out here!
Although now that I think about it,
Big Bro did feel a teeny
bit heavier than normal.
Hey you, it's the fishing pole!
You gotta hit the emergency brakes!
This entire train has been infected!
All the aches and pains are gone, but
something still doesn't feel right. What?
This guy's all better!
Are you even listening to me?
Tell the driver to stop the
train before we all bite him!
This can't be real.
If all these people are
starting to get better,
then the body that dropped
from my line must have been...
Oh god, no!
There's no way it was him!
No, Big Bro, please no!
Hey, I'm talking here!
Pay attention or we're
all gonna die, you idiot!
Big Bro Fusuto, say it as it's all!
What am I gonna do?
If he's not around, those guys
will come out of the turtle?
and that's it for me!
Achoo!
I gotta think of something!
Why are you crying like a damn baby?
Make somebody stop the train, strunzo!
Get in Mamoni out of the way if
you won't do anything to help.
I'll just have to do it myself
What's going on?
The aging hasn't stopped after all
But your auntie you're not again.
No, don't tell me
What?
Finish this.
Hurry, big boy. Bro!
Bro!
You were right, big bro.
Just like always, you
were absolutely right.
Once you've caught your target,
your only priority is to hold
on to them no matter what.
You have to keep your stand activated even
if it means you end up
losing an arm or a leg.
Oh, Big Bro.
With the state he's in, he
won't survive much longer.
He's a goner.
It's just a matter of time
before he takes his last breath.
And still he refuses
to withdraw his stand.
A warrior till the bitter end.
In order to complete our mission,
we have to capture Trish
whatever the personal cost.
Right, Big Bro?
We've come too close to the
finish light to turn back now.
I get it.
I understand, prosciutto.
You taught me true bravery.
I don't just hear your words now.
I feel them in the depths of my heart.
It's just like you
always told me, big bro.
When the dark dot comes,
the deed is already done.
Well, what do you know about that?
Taking life doesn't feel half bad.
It wasn't nearly as scary as
I thought it was gonna be.
And with that, my days of
being called Mamoni are over.
From now on, I'll be the pitiless
pesci of death feared by all.
I'm gonna put an end to
you once and for all.
While my big bro's powers
still have a little potency.
Bucciarati, you gotta get that hook
out of you before he retaliates!
Yeah?
So, you unzipped your hand, did you?
What?
Does this freak somehow have a way of
anticipating every move that I make?
I can read you like a picture book.
My hook's itching to get
inside and rip you apart,
and your wrist is too good
an entry point to pass up.
The hook's shooting up your
arm like a bat out of hell!
How'd it slip out again?
Merda!
Every time I go to pull it out, he anticipates
all my movements to the centimeter.
This guy's pretty good.
You've lost your mind if you think
I'll let you get away from me now.
I'll never let Big Bro Spirit die.
I'll snatch up Trish and complete
the mission in his honor.
Vucerati!
The dipshit's down there!
If we get rid of that guy, Churno and
the other guys will go back to normal.
After that, they can take down Po 'boy!
Understood.
But that's easier said than done.
You're about to get a helping of the
torment and anguish my Big Bro suffered!
Luchirazi!
Asshole must have grabbed onto something,
which would mean that he's climbing!
You're heading right for the power lines!
Now get me!
What's going on here?
I felt something hit, but it didn't
feel like a body being bisected.
I feel the vibrations of a pulse.
Bucciarati is definitely still alive.
He got himself back inside the train.
You lucked out, Bucciarati.
The way things are shaking out, we'll have
to take down this bastard face to face.
You're right.
But we don't have the
means. Not like this.
We've run out of time.
The hook is already burrowing
into my chest cavity. Oh, no!
My hook is 12 centimeters
away from your heart. Whoops.
Make that 11.
I misjudged terribly.
The thug with the aging
powers was formidable,
but I see now he was
never our greatest threat.
The real terror on the train was
hidden behind that innocuous tool.
What are you planning
to do now, Bucciarati?
That hook will skewer your
heart before too long.
Nine away, eight away.
I suppose I'll have to teach him a lesson.
The only way to overcome his stand is to
make this Koglione understand something.
I have Determinazione in spades!
Do it, Zipperman!
What the hell are you doing?
Bucciarati!
Huh?
He's gone!
Not even a hint of a pulse.
And I don't sense any breathing either.
But how?
I'm so confused.
How'd I completely lose track of him?
You're starting to worry me, Bucciarati.
I know we don't have a lot of
options, but this is too much.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Quiet yourself, number six.
We must wait till he leaves.
Acts like this are what it means to have.
Determinazione.
Dammit, he's gone!
His stand lets him slip off
my hook whenever he wants!
He could be anywhere!
He could ambush me from any angle!
No!
I gotta pull it together!
Paranoia is a sign of mental weakness!
That's what Prosciutto would tell me!
Be confident, Pesci.
If anyone can find a hidden heartbeat
on this speeding death trap from hell,
it's you, brother.
Damn straight!
There's no way Bucciarati is
as mobile as he used to be.
I bet big money that cowardly bastardo
is hiding out somewhere near my hook!
The line!
He's making it even longer now!
You've got to put yourself
back together and run!
I can't do that.
He still can't tell where I am.
And it'll stay that way as long
as I remain perfectly still.
Right now, I have to stay motionless.
That proves my resolve.
Listen for the blood
coursing through his veins.
Find his beating heart and destroy him.
Gotta catch.
But it's not the one I wanted.
The weight's all wrong.
It's a tourist!
It's fate, but there's no question.
It's a heart.
Not good!
He's zeroed in on your heart!
Muncherati!
You said all you were
gonna do was stay still,
not cleave your heart in
half to stop the vibrations!
Has he lost his mind?
No one can live for very long if their
heart and lungs don't work, right?
Dammit! Nothing!
This place is silent
as a freaking cemetery!
Slippery Katsone must have snuck off
somewhere with that zipper of his!
You've taken this too far!
What the hell?
Where is this bastard hiding now?
Huh?
Wait, what if that Gazzone Bucciarati
really finished off prosciutto?
If my bro's stand is gone, then the
guys in the turtle will be after me!
Damn it all!
Screw this noise!
You messed with the wrong guy!
We did it!
Poor idiot gave up and left!
That determinazione of yours totally
threw the Devi off the trail.
You sure as hell showed
that guy who's boss.
Now hurry up and zip
your body back together.
Come on, get a move on.
How strange life is.
What bad luck.
Just hang in there, Bucciarati.
Controlling bullets is
the most I'm able to do.
His drive got me totally off guard.
So, he's the victor.
Dammit!
Why won't this train stop?
Huh?
What's happening?
Becbrough, I'm coming!
That was a train ride from hell.
One that I would not have survived
without some luck on my side.
But I'm happy to say the
journey led me right to you.
You'll suffer for what
you've done, Bucciarati.
We got him!
Hell yeah for determinazione!
The last thing my big bro sees before he
dies will be your corpse
thrown into the wind.
Got it?
What the hell?
Consider me impressed.
You've got some sharp peepers.
That expression.
His eyes look like they've
witnessed years of bloodshed.
His composure is downright menacing.
Simple tricks aren't going to work on him.
Do it.
Glory is yours for the taking.
Finish him off, Pesci.
My time has come, but I'll be
watching you from the next life.
Make me proud.
I'll avenge my bro with your death!
What?
That's such a predictable move.
Ugh!
Shooting straight up the arm to the
cardiac muscle was always my Code.
Of course, that was when I didn't have
the balls to try anything riskier.
But now my finisher is an assault
straight to the heart of my prey.
Nothing will stop me from steamrolling
your brother-killing ass into extinction!
I'll rip your heart out and
tear it into a million pieces!
You should save the victory speech
until after you've won the fight.
That's how a true mafiosi does it.
Did I lose?
Is this really how I bite the big one?
No way.
Not before I play my ultimate hand.
Go ahead.
Take her and run. Wait now.
And I'll let her keep her life.
Look, he's got the turtle! What? Where?
I'm not gonna make it.
But before I go, the least I can do
is give you a little parting gift.
The gift of knowing
you failed your Family.
Now watch as I crush this
thing into turtle soup!
The rest of the group is
gonna be smashed to death!
You know, I admired
that glint in your eyes.
There was an unrelenting nobility to them.
You don't see that very often.
Pity, it's vanished.
Now you're nothing but a disgraced swine.
Am I now?
I disagree.
The only ones falling for grace are
your friends and this damn turtle!
It's over.
Enjoy burning in hell, Bucerati!
I can tell you've lived life
as the eternal screw-up.
Don't change on my account.
ARRIVA Trish
It's fairly obvious we can't
travel by train from here on out.
Yeah, I think you're right.
There's no telling what they know
and who they've told about us.
I'm sure they've figured out where we're
going by now, and what the Turtle can do.
We'll have to use another form
of transportation from here.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Would you be willing to cooperate?
Apologies, but we don't have
authorization to do such a thing.
You know our mission is
only to safeguard your life.
You will answer my questions.
Tell me, just who am I really?
What the hell is this?
How did it get on the ground?
I want answers.
Why are these bizarre marks
appearing near my feet?
How did a father I've never even
met turn me into a walking target?
As I thought, the boss's
daughter is a stand user.
Well, answer me!
It's currently 6.34 p .m.
I arrived at the scene 20
minutes after the train stopped.
Prosciutto is dead next to the tracks.
Pesci has been mutilated.
The pieces are scattered
near the riverbed.
Judging from the bloodbath here, this must
be the work of Bucciaranti's Zipperman.
And what about his team and the girl?
Long gone.
Can you track him, Melone? Yes.
Those two disfigured losers actually
managed to do something useful for once.
I've got a decent blood sample now.
From Bucciarati.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see!
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me!
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need!
I need your body.
Tell me.
What must I do?
To show how much
I'm a freak in you?
What must I do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To show how much I'm a freak in you?
Thank you.
You